As Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for those afflicted with various sicknesses
and diseases in the Peru crusade, the chains of bondage in their lives are broken
as the power of Jesus Christ is clearly present on the scene.
I have pain in my coccyx.
Man of God, I want to be healed!
Knee trauma has left this lady confined to a wheelchair.
But with just a simple touch from the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua,
in the name of Jesus Christ, she begins to walk to the glory of God.
Healed In Jesus' Name
The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed In Jesus' Name
CRUSADE IN PERU
WITH T.B. JOSHUA
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Ysela Juarez Carranza
Lima, Peru
I am 41 years old.
As a result of an accident, I developed a knee problem and was unable to walk.
The prognosis from the doctor said that the problem was congenital.
I was unable to walk and I also had a problem with my coccyx.
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
For how long have you been having this problem?
Four years.
I went to four hospitals, two clinics and ultimately, they did not know the exact problem I had.
The last doctor I went to said that because I was born with the knee condition,
I needed an operation but there was no guarantee it would fix the problem I had.
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
It was very difficult.
My knees would swell up and I felt a lot of pain in my coccyx.
I couldn't walk; I needed other people to assist me.
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
What happened at the crusade when Prophet T.B. Joshua put his hand on you?
The prophet put his hand on my head, on my knees which were very swollen
and on my back and told me to walk.
How did you feel right after the crusade?
I feel really good.
I thank God.
Are you still using the wheelchair?
I am not using it.
I walk normally; I could not run or climb stairs in a normal way.
Can you please show us what you can do right now?
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Yes and I can run too!
Mrs Ysela runs to the glory of God
because she no longer has the knee trauma that she once had before.
Thank You, Jesus!
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 15/02/2019